<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<cheatsheet
      title="Introduction to Scala">
   <intro>
      <description>
         This tutorial will get you started with using <b>Scala</b> in the Eclipse IDE.<br/><br/>
You will learn how to create a new Scala application, and how to run and debug it.
      </description>
   </intro>
   <item
         title="Switch to the Scala perspective">
      <description>
         Let&apos;s start by switching to the <b>Scala perspective</b>. This brings in all the Scala-related views and menus.
     </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective(org.eclipse.ui.perspectives.showPerspective.perspectiveId=org.scala-ide.sdt.core.perspective)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Create a Scala project">
      <description>
         Next, let&apos;s ceate a Scala project. A Scala project holds together related source files and configuration (like classpath and compiler settings).
<br/><br/>
Everything you do in Eclipse is based on a project.
<br/><br/>
Click below to create a project. Choose a name and click <b>Finish</b>.
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=org.scala-ide.sdt.core.wizards.newProject)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         skip="false"
         title="Create a Scala object">
      <description>
         Let&apos;s start by creating a Scala object that extends <b>App</b>.
<br/><br/>
Unlike Java, Scala has top-level <b>objects</b>. A top-level object is a singleton, and it is initialized on first access. By making an object extend <b>App</b>, we make it <b>runnable</b>: everything inside the object will be executed.
<br/><br/>
Right click on the project and select <b>New Scala Object</b>.
Make sure to choose the source folder in the project you just created. Also, enter a name for the object, like <b>Main</b> and a <b>package</b> name. The corresponding folders will be created for you.
<br/><br/>
<b>Using the default (empty) package is strongly discouraged.</b>
      </description>
      <command
            required="false"
            serialization="org.eclipse.ui.newWizard(newWizardId=org.scala-ide.sdt.core.wizards.newObject)"/>
   </item>
   <item
         title="Run a Scala program">
      <description>
         Let&apos;s add some code and run the program.<br/><br/>
<b>println(&quot;Hello, world&quot;)</b>
<br/><br/>
Now right click and choose <b>Run As &gt; Scala Application</b>. You should see the output in the <b>Console</b> window.
      </description>
   </item>
</cheatsheet>
